Sujatali M Shaikh

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India



shujaatfirst@gmail.com



9820782262



linkedin.com/in/sujatali-m-shaikh-0013161a

Summary

Experienced Solutions Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in SaaS based implementation, Customer Relationship Management (CRM), Account Management, graduate from M K institute of Computer studies (BCA) Bharuch Gujarat.

Experience



Assistant Vice President

Poonawalla Finance

May 2021 - Present (1 month +)

Manage IT Applications - Leadsquared, Finnone etc.

Streamlining Existing Business Process

Implementing New Processes in Leadsquared Platform



Lead Business Analyst

LeadSquared

Nov 2017 - Apr 2021 (3 years 6 months)

Handle Key Enterprise Clients like Poonawalla Finance, Kotak Group, Group Satellite, Kolte Patil, Metropolis etc.

End to End implementation from Project planning to Go Live.

Building robust custom solutions as per business needs

Training Clients on Leadsquared Product



Technical Analyst

Talisma

May 2014 - Oct 2017 (3 years 6 months)

Talisma CRM product implementation, upgrading the existing setup, hardware sizing, End to End support, Gathering new requirements from the customers and get it developed in Talisma using various technologies like BIDS, SSMS,IIS.

Other Activities: Database backup/restore, Managing backup, Attach/Detach Database, Reindexing, Monitoring system. Server management, DBA activities, Building Queries, Troubleshooting.

Also have good hands on MS SQL Server 2012.

Assistant Manager

IndusInd Bank

Aug 2010 - Apr 2014 (3 years 9 months)

Ssis packages build debug execute! L2 support for talisma application, inhouse development, database administration, creating schedule jobs, liaise with business team for new project requirement, uat testing, managing users across pan india, create talisma sql jobs.

Education



M K institute of Computer studies (BCA) Bharuch Gujarat

BCA

2005 - 2008

Licenses & Certifications



Oracle 9i Database Administrator - Oracle



Business Analysis Foundations - LinkedIn

Skills

Microsoft SQL Server • SQL • SSIS • CRM • Databases • Microsoft Office • Team Management • Java • Management • Business Analysis